travelexperta.com 2017-08-19

# Reviews for Travel Products, Hotels, Restaurants and Tours

[Travelexperta.com](http://travelexperta.com/) is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit the site. You can access Travel Experta and browse the site without disclosing any of your personal data. I do not collect personal information about individuals, such as names and mailing or e-mail addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual and he or she has agreed to the terms under which Travel Experta will use it.

**Disclosure of Information**  
Travelexperta.com will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. I do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We may use IP addresses to compile and provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and administer the site. This statistical information may also be related to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We collect only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

If you do not want to have your information used in this way, send an e-mail message containing your name and email address to marinakuperman@gmail.com.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to me. For that reason, I do not collect or maintain information at my site from those I actually know are under 18.

**External Web Sites**  
Please note that travelexperta.com contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage the users to be aware that when they leave the site that you read the privacy statements of each web site that might collect personally identifying information.

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by travelexperta.com. If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy policy, please contact: marinakuperman@gmail.com.

  *   *   *   *   *   * 

## About Marina Kuperman Villatoro

[Marina Kuperman Villatoro](https://plus.google.com/u/0/114721413075206411121) CEO of [TravelExperta.com](http://travelexperta.com//), a travel resource site to inspire families to travel with kids of all ages. Marina has been an expat 10+ years in Central America raising 2 boys in a multicultural, trilingual household. She travels all over the world with her family to give first hand experiences of where to eat, stay and play with kids. Needless to say, it’s never boring! Join Marina on [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/travelexperta) and [Twitter](https://twitter.com/#%21/MarinaVillatoro) for more unique and boutique family travel!
